It's for you
Es por ti
That destiny brought me here
Que el destino me trajo hasta aquí
To dance
Para bailar
Dance this bachata, my love
Bailar esta bachata, mi amor
Come next to me, my heart
Ven a mi lado, corazón
Dance with me slowly
Baila conmigo suavemente
All my life I've searched for you
Toda mi vida te busqué
You're my dream of a woman, my dream of a woman
Eres mi sueño de mujer, mi sueño de mujer
To dance this bachata is what unleashes me
Bailar esta bachata es lo que me desata
With you next to me
Contigo a mi lado
The only thing that I want is dance
Lo único que quiero es bailar
Dance this bachata (dance this bachata)
Bailar esta bachata (bailar esta bachata)
Dance this bachata is what unleashes me
Bailar esta bachata es lo que me desata
With you next to me
Contigo a mi lado
The only thing that I want is dance
Lo único que quiero es bailar
Dance this bachata
Bailar esta bachata
Hola bonita! I like your look
¡Hola, bonita!, ich steh' auf deinen Look
No designers, but everyone here watches
Keine Designer, doch jeder hier guckt
The lips are red, they match the dress
Rot sind die Lippen, sie passen zum Kleid
Love your curves, bachata the vibe
Lieb' deine Kurven, Bachata der Vibe
Baby, te quiero, 'cause you're not looking for Dinero
Baby, te quiero, denn du schaust nicht auf Dinero
Other women interest me zero
Andere Frauen interessieren mich zero
Can't handle your body
Komm' auf dei'm Body nicht klar
Face like a Hollywood star
Gesicht wie ein Hollywoodstar
Let it be you hottest summer night
Lass es dir heißeste Sommernacht sein
The bartender brings us Moloko with ice cream
Der Barkeeper bringt uns Moloko mit Eis
Just you and me, we forget the time
Nur du und ich, wir vergessen die Zeit
When you shake your hips, everyone knows, yeah
Schwingst du die Hüften, weiß jeder Bescheid, yeah
Every movement is suavemente
Jede Bewegung ist suavemente
Rhythm in the blood, caliente
Rhythmus im Blut, caliente
Hope the evening ends with you
Hoffe, dass mit dir der Abend endet
Come next to me, my heart (come next to me, my heart)
Ven a mi lado, corazón (ven a mi lado, corazón)
Dance with me slowly (dance with me slowly)
Baila conmigo suavemente (baila conmigo suavemente)
All my life I've searched for you
Toda mi vida te busqué (toda mi vida te busqué)
You're my dream of a woman, my dream of a woman
Eres mi sueño de mujer, mi sueño de mujer
Dance this bachata is what unleashes me
Bailar esta bachata es lo que me desata
With you next to me
Contigo a mi lado
The only thing that I want is dance
Lo único que quiero es bailar (oh yeah)
Dance this bachata (dance this bachata, my love)
Bailar esta bachata (bailar esta bachata, mi amor)
Dance this bachata is what unleashes me (dance this bachata)
Bailar esta bachata es lo que me desata (bailar esta bachata)
With you next to me
Contigo a mi lado
The only thing I want is dance (the only thing I want)
Lo único que quiero es bailar (lo único que quiero)
Dance this bachata (dance this bachata)
Bailar esta bachata (bailar esta bachata)
[INVALID]
[INVALID]